Guide to the Amsterdam News photograph archive, Series A. Subject Files F-J, 1920-2012.
Amsterdam News photograph archive
- Series A. Subject Files
  - Subject Files H
    - Hill, Gloria (Box A-56, Folder 232)
      Note on folder: "also here is Greg Hill."
      Photographer if identified: Beake-Huntungton Inc
    - Hill, Grant (Box A-56, Folder 233)
    - Hill, Greg (Box A-56, Folder 234)
    - Hill, Howard (Box A-56, Folder 235)
    - Hill, Hector W. (Box A-56, Folder 236)
    - Hill, Henry (Box A-56, Folder 237)
    - Hill, Henry A. (Dr.) (Box A-56, Folder 238)
    - Hill, Herb (Box A-56, Folder 239)
      Photographer if identified: Curt Clemons Foto, Bert Andrews
    - Hill, Herman (Box A-56, Folder 240)
    - Hill, Hilton (Box A-56, Folder 241)
    - Hill, Horatio (Dr.) (Box A-56, Folder 242)
      One print has two staples in the border.
    - Hill, Hugh (Box A-56, Folder 243)
    - Hill, Jackie (Box A-56, Folder 244)
    - Hill, Jeremiah (Rev.) (Box A-56, Folder 245)
    - Hill, Jesse, Jr. (Box A-56, Folder 246)
      Photographer if identified: Delta Airlines Atlanta Airport, Dawoud Bey
    - Hill, John (Box A-56, Folder 247)
    - Hill, John Q. (Box A-56, Folder 248)
    - Hill, Joyce (Mrs.) (Box A-56, Folder 249)
    - Hill, Kenneth D. (Box A-56, Folder 250)
    - Hill, L. E. (Box A-56, Folder 251)
    - Hill, Larry (Box A-56, Folder 252)
    - Hill, Lauren (Box A-56, Folder 253)
    - Hill, Lawrence (Box A-56, Folder 254)
      Photographer if identified: Surlock
    - Hill Lena M. (Box A-56, Folder 255)
      Photographer if identified: Frank Braden
    - Hill, Leroy (Box A-56, Folder 256)
      Photographer if identified: Wagner International Photos Inc
    - Hill, Lester (Box A-56, Folder 257)
      Photographer if identified: Barnes Associates
    - Hill, Lisa (Box A-56, Folder 258)
    - Hill, Marshall (Box A-56, Folder 259)
      Photographer if identified: Roy Blakey
    - Hill, Michael (Box A-56, Folder 260)
    - Hill, Michael & Johnnie (Box A-56, Folder 261)
      Name on verso of print is "The Hill Twins." Also one velox print.
    - Hill, Norman (Box A-56, Folder 262)
      Photographer if identified: K. Y. Owusu
    - Hill, Otis O. (Box A-56, Folder 263)
    - Hill, Philbert D. (Mrs.) (Box A-56, Folder 264)
      Note on folder: "see Hudgens, Alvin D. (Mrs.)."
    - Hill, Rena (Box A-56, Folder 265)
    - Hill, Robert (Box A-56, Folder 266)
    - Hill, Robert (Box A-56, Folder 267)
      Name on recto of print is "Robert A. Hill."
    - Hill, Romelia (Box A-56, Folder 268)
      Note of folder: "also Ronald Hill." One print has a staple through the border.
      Photographer if identified: Matt Grimaldi
    - Hill, Roy L. (Box A-56, Folder 269)
      One print is affixed to cardboard backing by tape.
    - Hill, Ruby (Box A-56, Folder 270)
    - Hill, Ruth Lois (Box A-56, Folder 271)
      Both prints affixed to one cardboard backing with glue.
    - Hill, Stanley (Box A-56, Folder 272)
    - Hill, Tainy (Box A-56, Folder 273)
    - Hill, Tessie (Box A-56, Folder 274)
    - Hill, Thaddeus (Box A-56, Folder 275)
      Note on folder: "Also here Mrs. Thelma Goodrich Hill."
    - Hill, Thelma (Ms.) (Box A-56, Folder 276)
    - Hill, Thelma Goodrich (Box A-56, Folder 277)
    - Hill, Thomas (Box A-56, Folder 278)
      Print has paint on the recto.
    - Hill, Timothy (Box A-56, Folder 279)
    - Hill Twins, The (Box A-56, Folder 280)
      One print is attached to two carbonscript leaves by two staples.
    - Hill, Valdema A. (Box A-56, Folder 281)
    - Hill, Velma (Box A-56, Folder 282)
      Photographer if identified: Dan Miller
    - Hill, Waddell (Box A-56, Folder 283)
      One print is affixed to cardstock backing by tape.
      Photographer if identified: Miss Lee Luckett, Alvin J. Burley
    - Hill, William (Rev.) (Box A-56, Folder 284)
      Photographer if identified: Inwood News Photo Service
    - Hill, William G. (Box A-56, Folder 285)
    - Hill, Willie L. (Rev.) (Box A-56, Folder 286)
    - Hill, Wilmac (Box A-56, Folder 287)
    - Hill, Winston (Box A-56, Folder 288)
    - Hill-Slater, Phyllis (Box A-56, Folder 289)
    - Hilland, Joe (Box A-56, Folder 290)
    - Hilland, Karen (Box A-56, Folder 291)
    - Hillary, Wayne (Box A-56, Folder 292)
    - Hillbilly Club, The (Box A-56, Folder 293)
    - Hille, Alice (Box A-56, Folder 294)
    - Hilliard, David (Box A-56, Folder 295)
      Note on folder: "Panther Chief."
      Photographer if identified: United Press International, Wide World Photos
    - Hllliard, Sheryl L. (Box A-56, Folder 296)
      Note on folder: "Managing editor for Black Enterprise Magazine." One print has a staple in the border.
    - Hillman, George (Box A-56, Folder 297)
      One print contains two images. One print is cut from a larger image.
    - Hillman, Olive (Box A-56, Folder 298)
      Print is attached ms. Leaf by staple.
    - Hillman, Ponsie (Box A-56, Folder 299)
    - Hillson, Abram (Box A-56, Folder 300)
    - Hilly, John (Box A-56, Folder 301)
    - Hilton, Charrise (Box A-56, Folder 302)
      One print is attached to carbonscript note by straight pin. One print has ms. Note on verso attached by glue.
      Photographer if identified: James Samuels, Harold T. Cooper
    - Hilton, Lawrence (Box A-56, Folder 303)
    - Hilton, Roy (Box A-56, Folder 304)
      Print is attached to typescript press release leaf by tape.
    - Hilton, Shirlee (Mrs.) (Box A-56, Folder 305)
    - Hilton, Solomon (Box A-56, Folder 306)
      Photographer if identified: Arnold Hinton
    - Hilton Jacobs, Lawrence (Box A-56, Folder 307)
      Also two velox prints, of which one has a caption stuck to the recto.
    - Himes, Chester (Box A-56, Folder 308)
    - Hinderas, Natalie (Box A-56, Folder 309)
    - Hinds, Conrade (Box A-56, Folder 310)
    - Hinds, Davis (Box A-56, Folder 311)
    - Hinds, Esther (Box A-56, Folder 312)
      Photographer if identified: Beth Bergman, Ellen Jacobs
    - Hinds, Glester (Box A-57, Folder 1)
      One color Polaroid print. Also one velox print. A group of about six prints are grouped together with a paperclip.
      Photographer if identified: A. Hansen, Harris Photo, YMCA of Greater New York/Public Relations Department, Bro. David McAdams, Big M, Tex Harris, P.G. Franklin
    - Hinds, Glester (Box A-57, Folder 2)
    - Hinds, Herbert (Box A-57, Folder 3)
    - Hinds, John (Box A-57, Folder 4)
      Photographer if identified: The Picture Desk/Publicity Photographs
    - Hinds, Julie (Box A-57, Folder 5)
    - Hinds, Lennox S. (Box A-57, Folder 6)
    - Hinds, Rudolph (Box A-57, Folder 7)
      Photographer if identified: Beth Brian Staulcup
    - Hinds, Ruby (Box A-57, Folder 8)
    - Hinds Sisters (Box A-57, Folder 9)
    - Hinds, Vira C. (Box A-57, Folder 10)
    - Hines, Alfreda (Box A-57, Folder 11)
    - Hines Brothers and Chink Hines (Box A-57, Folder 12)
    - Hines, Carlos (Mr. and Mrs.) (Box A-57, Folder 13)
    - Hines, Corine (Box A-57, Folder 14)
    - Hines, Earl (Box A-57, Folder 15)
      Also five velox prints.
      Photographer if identified: E. Leshin, Harris Photo, Sabena/Belgian World Airlines, TWA/John F. Kennedy International Airport
    - Hines, Earl Septet (Box A-57, Folder 16)
      Photographer if identified: Hi-Cue Productions Inc.
    - Hines, Elbert (Box A-57, Folder 17)
      Print is badly darkened and giving off a chemical odor.
    - Hines Family (Box A-57, Folder 18)
    - Hines, Frances (Mr. and Mrs.) (Box A-57, Folder 19)
    - Hines, Henry L., Jr. (Box A-57, Folder 20)
    - Hines, John (Rev.) (Box A-57, Folder 21)
    - Hines, Gregory (Box A-57, Folder 22)
    - Hines, Justin (Box A-57, Folder 23)
    - Hines, Lorna (Box A-57, Folder 24)
    - Hines, Marcia (Box A-57, Folder 25)
      Photographer if identified: Australian Information Service/Eric Wadsworth
    - Hines, Laura "Babe", (also) Mrs. Marcia Hines (Box A-57, Folder 26)
      Image of Laura Hines appears on a commercial card reading "Season's Greetings" on the recto.
    - Hines, Marguerite (Box A-57, Folder 27)
    - Hines, Nathaniel L. (Box A-57, Folder 28)
    - Hines, Needon J. (Box A-57, Folder 29)
    - Hines, Samuel (Rev.) (Box A-57, Folder 30)
    - Hines, Shirley (Box A-57, Folder 31)
    - Hines, Stanley (Rev.) (Box A-57, Folder 32)
    - Hines, Wattell (Box A-57, Folder 33)
    - Hinkson, Egbert (Box A-57, Folder 34)
    - Hinkson, Elbert C. (Hon.) (Box A-57, Folder 35)
    - Hinkson, Mary (Box A-57, Folder 36)
      Photographer if identified: Norma McLain Stoop, Brooklyn Academy of Music/Press Department
    - Hinkson, Montgomery (Box A-57, Folder 37)
    - Hinkson, Vernese (Box A-57, Folder 38)
    - Hinnard, Ollen B. (Box A-57, Folder 39)
    - Hinson, Alfred L. (Box A-57, Folder 40)
    - Hinson, Andy (Box A-57, Folder 41)
    - Hinson, Anthony (Box A-57, Folder 42)
      Photographer if identified: Robert J. Eckman
    - Hinson, Ophelia (Box A-57, Folder 43)
    - Hinton, Algia Mae (Box A-57, Folder 44)
    - Hinton, Chuck (Box A-57, Folder 45)
    - Hinton, Eddie (Box A-57, Folder 46)
    - Hinton, J. (Box A-57, Folder 47)
    - Hinton, Junius (Box A-57, Folder 48)
    - Hinton, Michael P. (Box A-57, Folder 49)
    - Hinton, Milton (Box A-57, Folder 50)
    - Hinton, Susan (Box A-57, Folder 51)
    - Hinton, Warren (Box A-57, Folder 52)
    - Hintzen, Gage (Box A-57, Folder 53)
    - Hiram Walker (Box A-57, Folder 54)
      Photographer if identified: Ernest Agnew, Pope Studio, Guy's Photography
    - Hirschfield, Abe (Box A-57, Folder 55)
    - Hirt, Al (Box A-57, Folder 56)
    - Hiroshima (Box A-57, Folder 57)
    - His and Her Social Club (Box A-57, Folder 58)
      Photographer if identified: Bob Head, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise
    - Hisle, Larry (Box A-57, Folder 59)
      Photographer if identified: United Press International Photos
    - Historical Research Society (Box A-57, Folder 60)
    - "Hitch" (Box A-57, Folder 61)
    - Hitch, Jewett (Mrs.) (Box A-57, Folder 62)
    - Hitchcock, Alfred (Box A-57, Folder 63)
    - Hitchhikers, The (Box A-57, Folder 64)
    - Hoall, Ed (Box A-57, Folder 65)
    - Hoard, Adrienne W. (Box A-57, Folder 66)
      Photographer if identified: Frank Stewart
    - Hoard, Samuel L. (Rev.) and family (Box A-57, Folder 67)
    - Hobbes, Marjorie (Box A-57, Folder 68)
    - Hobbs, Alfred (Box A-57, Folder 69)
    - Hobbs, Cecilia (Box A-57, Folder 70)
    - Hobbs, John (Box A-57, Folder 71)
    - Hobby, Gladys L. (Dr.) (Box A-57, Folder 72)
      Photographer if identified: Bradford Bachrach
    - Hobdy, Fred (Box A-57, Folder 73)
    - Hobson, Ann (Box A-57, Folder 74)
    - Hobson, Charles (Mr.) (Box A-57, Folder 75)
    - Hobson, Ernest E. (Box A-57, Folder 76)
    - Hobson, James (Sgt.) (Box A-57, Folder 77)
    - Hobson, Lorraine (Box A-57, Folder 78)
    - Hobson, Paulette (Box A-57, Folder 79)
    - Hobson, Susan (Box A-57, Folder 80)
    - Hobson, Verna (Box A-57, Folder 81)
    - Hodge, Bob (Box A-57, Folder 82)
    - Hodge, Gerald E. (Box A-57, Folder 83)
    - Hodge, Gerald E., Sr. (Box A-57, Folder 84)
      Photographer if identified: Studio Five/Miles Raymond
    - Hodge, John E. (Box A-57, Folder 85)
    - Hodge, Ollie Akins (Mrs.) (Box A-57, Folder 86)
    - Hodge, Jeanette (Box A-57, Folder 87)
    - Hodge, Melvin (Box A-57, Folder 88)
    - Hodges, Arthur (Box A-57, Folder 89)
    - Hodges, Brenda (Box A-57, Folder 90)
    - Hodges, Bruce (Box A-57, Folder 91)
      Photographer if identified: Gerald M. Goldberg/Director of Public Relations/WINS
    - Hodges, Bruce A. (Box A-57, Folder 92)
    - Hodges, Charles (Box A-57, Folder 93)
    - Hodges, David, Jr. (Box A-57, Folder 94)
    - Hodges, Grant (Box A-57, Folder 95)
    - Hodges, James and Smith (Box A-57, Folder 96)
    - Hodges, James and Smith (Box A-57, Folder 97)
    - Hodge, Jeanette (Box A-57, Folder 98)
    - Hodges, Johnny (Box A-57, Folder 99)
    - Hodges, Johnny (Box A-57, Folder 100)
    - Hodges, Luther B. (Box A-57, Folder 101)
    - Hodges, Virgil H. (Box A-57, Folder 102)
    - Hodgin, Andora (Box A-57, Folder 103)
    - Hodgson, Carlton R. (Box A-57, Folder 104)
    - Hoe, Virginia (Box A-57, Folder 105)
    - Hoeller, John (Box A-57, Folder 106)
    - Hoenig, Peggy (Box A-57, Folder 107)
    - Hoffer, Mildred (Mrs.) (Box A-57, Folder 108)
    - Hoffler, Mildred (Box A-57, Folder 109)
    - Hoffman, Dustin (Box A-57, Folder 110)
      Includes one group of 15 prints paperclipped together.
    - Hoffman, Thomas (Box A-57, Folder 111)
    - Hofford, William H. (Box A-57, Folder 112)
      Photographer if identified: New York Community Training Institute
    - Hogan, Albert (Box A-57, Folder 113)
    - Hogan, Frank S. (District Attorney) (Box A-57, Folder 114)
    - Hogan, Henrietta (Box A-57, Folder 115)
    - Hogan, Phillip (Box A-57, Folder 116)
    - Hogan, Roxy C. (Box A-57, Folder 117)
    - Hogan, William (Mrs.) (Box A-57, Folder 118)
    - Hoge, Sarah (Box A-57, Folder 119)
    - Hoggard, J. Clinton (Bishop) (Box A-57, Folder 120)
      Photographer if identified: J. Peltz, Livingstone College/Public Relations Department
    - Hoggard, Jay (Box A-57, Folder 121)
    - Hoque, Paul (Box A-57, Folder 122)
      Photographer if identified: William R. Whitteker
    - Hoist, Vincent (Box A-57, Folder 123)
    - Hoke, George (Rev.) (Box A-57, Folder 124)
    - Holbert, Annette and Emerson (Box A-57, Folder 125)
    - Holbert, Emerson (see: Holbert, Annette) (Box A-57, Folder 126)
    - Holbert, Kenneth F. (Box A-57, Folder 127)
    - Holcomb, Alfonso (Box A-57, Folder 128)
    - Holcomb, Beatrice (Box A-57, Folder 129)
    - Holcomb, C.M. (Box A-57, Folder 130)
    - Holcombe, Rucker Basketball (Box A-57, Folder 131)
    - Holder, Christian (Box A-57, Folder 132)
      Photographer if identified: Herm Migdoll
    - Holden, Chuck and Betty (Box A-57, Folder 133)
    - Holden, Dorothy (Dr.) (Box A-57, Folder 134)
      Photographer if identified: Bob West, State University of New York/Downstate Medical Center/Office of Public Affairs Box 2
    - Holden, Peter G. (Box A-57, Folder 135)
    - Holden, Ronald (Box A-57, Folder 136)
    - Holder, Christian (Box A-57, Folder 137)
      Photographer if identified: Herb Migdoll
    - Holder, Geneva Penn (Dr.) (deceased) (Box A-57, Folder 138)
      Photographer if identified: Cecil Layne, Negro Press Photo Service Inc.
    - Holder, James (Box A-57, Folder 139)
    - Holder, John H. (Box A-57, Folder 140)
    - Holder, Lofton (Box A-57, Folder 141)
    - Holder, Geoffrey (Box A-57, Folder 142)
      Photographer if identified: Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, Harris Photo, Pictorial Enterprise, Hakim, Peterkin Photo, Simon Lewis/Human Resources
    - Holder, Mark (Box A-57, Folder 143)
    - Holder, Marylynn (Box A-57, Folder 144)
    - Holder, Peter, Sr. (Box A-57, Folder 145)
    - Holder, Randolph S. (Rev.) (Box A-57, Folder 146)
    - Holder, Rueben (Box A-57, Folder 147)
    - Holder, Samuel R. (Rev.) (Box A-57, Folder 148)
      Photographer if identified: Bob Wheeler, Pictorial Enterprise, Gill Photographers
    - Holder, Stephen (Box A-57, Folder 149)
    - Holder, Vivian (Mrs.) (Box A-57, Folder 150)
    - Holder, Wesley McD (Box A-57, Folder 151)
      Photographer if identified: Hamilton
    - Holeman, Andrew L. (Lt.) (Box A-57, Folder 152)
    - Holgate, Perkins and Shaw (Box A-57, Folder 153)
    - Holiday, Billie (See Inactive File near Cuts) (Box A-57, Folder 154)
    - Holiday, Billie (Box A-57, Folder 155)
    - Billie Holiday Theatre (Box A-57, Folder 156)
      Also one velox print, folder in half.
    - Holiday, Jennifer (Box A-57, Folder 157)
    - Holiday, Louis A. (Rev.) (Box A-57, Folder 158)
    - Holiday, Wilhelmina (Box A-57, Folder 159)
    - Holkman, Loretta (Box A-57, Folder 160)
      Photographer if identified: Donovan Kirven/Scott Woods
    - Holland (Box A-57, Folder 161)
    - Holland, Albert (Box A-57, Folder 162)
    - Holland, Carolyn Patricia Martin (Box A-57, Folder 163)
    - Holland, Charles (Box A-57, Folder 164)
      Photographer if identified: Fotocentrum (Amsterdam), Symphony of the New World
    - Holland, Cora (Box A-57, Folder 165)
    - Holland, Debra (Box A-57, Folder 166)
    - Holland, Debrah Ann (Box A-57, Folder 167)
    - Holland-Dozier-Holland (Box A-57, Folder 168)
    - Holland, Eddie (Box A-57, Folder 169)
    - Holland, Edna (Box A-57, Folder 170)
    - Holland, Endesha Ida Mae (Box A-57, Folder 171)
    - Holland, George (Box A-57, Folder 172)
    - Holland, Jerome (Dr.) (Box A-57, Folder 173)
      Many prints have single-leaf typescript or carbon captions adhered to the versos or loose Also five velox prints.
      Photographer if identified: Hampton Institute/Office of Public Relations, James Gilbert, Fabian Bachrach, Jet Commercial Photographers, Union Carbide Corporation, Irving Newman
    - Holland, Jerome (Dr.) (Box A-57, Folder 174)
      Photographer if identified: ARC in Greater N.Y.
    - Holland, Lawarence (Box A-57, Folder 175)
    - Holland, Luther, Jr. (Box A-57, Folder 176)
    - Holland, Ronald (Mr. and Mrs.) (Box A-57, Folder 177)
    - Holland, Wilfred H. (Box A-57, Folder 178)
      Photographer if identified: Ken A. Campbell
    - Hollav, Lloyd (Box A-57, Folder 179)
    - Holley, Bill (Box A-57, Folder 180)
    - Holley, Earl J. (Marine Sgt.) (Box A-57, Folder 181)
    - Holley, Edgar M. (Box A-57, Folder 182)
    - Holley, Hazel (Box A-57, Folder 183)
    - Holley, Josephine (Box A-57, Folder 184)
    - Holley, Major (Box A-57, Folder 185)
    - Holliday, Bernard (Rev.) (Box A-57, Folder 186)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, King Photographers
    - Holliday, Billie (Box A-57, Folder 187)
      (See also: Holiday, Billie)
    - Holliday, Coniel (Box A-57, Folder 188)
    - Holliday, Jennifer-Yvette (Box A-57, Folder 189)
      Photographer if identified: P. Cunningham, Pictorial Enterprise
    - Holliday, Odell (Box A-57, Folder 190)
      Black and white Polaroid print.
    - Hollingsworth, Alta (Box A-57, Folder 191)
    - Hollingsworth, Alvin C. (Box A-57, Folder 192)
      Photographer if identified: Allen Schill, Pictorial Enterprise
    - Hollingsworth, James (Box A-57, Folder 193)
    - Hollins, Gerri (Box A-57, Folder 194)
    - Hollins, Juda (Box A-57, Folder 195)
    - Hollins, Leo (Box A-57, Folder 196)
    - Hollins, Warren (Box A-57, Folder 197)
    - Hollis, Marcus Gibson (Box A-57, Folder 198)
    - Hollis, Meldon S., Jr. (Box A-57, Folder 199)
    - Hollis, Olivia (Mrs.) (See Mrs. Charles Stewart) (Box A-57, Folder 200)
    - Hollis, Ralph and Bessie (Box A-57, Folder 201)
    - Hollis, Ronnie (Box A-57, Folder 202)
    - Holloman, Charlotte (Miss) (Box A-57, Folder 203)
      Photographer if identified: Fred Harris
    - Holloman, Charlotte W. (Box A-57, Folder 204)
      Photographer if identified: Richard H. Barrett, Pan American World Airways/Overseas Division
    - Holloman, John L.S., Jr. (Dr.) (Box A-57, Folder 205)
      Also six velox prints. Many prints have typescript captions or bios adhered or attached to prints.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, United Hospital Fund, Scurlock, Scott L. Henderson, Robert Reilly
    - Holloman, John L.S., Jr. (Dr.) (Box A-57, Folder 206)
      Also four velox prints. Also three duplicate single-leaf press releases from the March of Dimes, and about five other single-leaf typescript releases, loose or attached to prints.
      Photographer if identified: Virginia Union University, Harris Photo, Greene DeVito, City of New York/Department of Sanitation, A. Hansen, Bert Carpenter, Dave Greene, Ralph Cooper, M Associates, Verna, Richard H. Barrett.
    - Holloman, John L.S., Jr. (Dr.) (Box A-57, Folder 207)
    - Holloman, Pat (Box A-57, Folder 208)
      Photographer if identified: Richard Lee
    - Holloman, Rita (Box A-57, Folder 209)
    - Hollon, Herbert A. (Box A-57, Folder 210)
      Photographer if identified: Ron Magarro/Modern Photography
    - Hollon, Wilber (Skippy) (See Mable Taylor) (Box A-57, Folder 211)
    - Holloway, Anthony (Box A-57, Folder 212)
    - Holloway, Bernice (Box A-57, Folder 213)
    - Holloway, Buria (Box A-57, Folder 214)
    - Holloway, Floyd (Box A-57, Folder 215)
    - Holloway, Hiliary H. (Box A-57, Folder 216)
    - Holloway, Jesse (Box A-57, Folder 217)
    - Holloway, (Joe and Family) (Box A-57, Folder 218)
    - Holloway, Loleatta (Box A-57, Folder 219)
      Photographer if identified: Bill Price Jr.
    - Holloway, Lou Emma (Box A-57, Folder 220)
    - Holloway, Nancy (Box A-57, Folder 221)
    - Holloway, Patricia (Box A-57, Folder 222)
    - Holloway, Thomasine (Box A-57, Folder 223)
    - Holloway, William J. (Box A-57, Folder 224)
    - Holloway, William L. (Box A-57, Folder 225)
    - Hollowell, Donald L. (Box A-57, Folder 226)
    - Hollowell, Donald L. (Box A-57, Folder 227)
    - Hollowell, Ronald (Box A-57, Folder 228)
    - Holly, Ann Karen (Box A-57, Folder 229)
    - Holly, Betty (Box A-57, Folder 230)
    - Holly, Ellen (Box A-57, Folder 231)
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Bert Andrews
    - Holly, Karen (Box A-57, Folder 232)
      Photographer if identified: Safford
    - Holly, John O. (Box A-57, Folder 233)
    - Holly, Major (Box A-57, Folder 234)
      Photographer if identified: Ted Davis
    - Holly, Ronald (Box A-57, Folder 235)
    - Holly, Ronnie (Box A-57, Folder 236)
    - Hollywood Baptist Church (Box A-57, Folder 237)
      One print is badly darkened and giving off a chemical odor.
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert/News Voice International, Photo Courtesy A.I.D./Agency for International Development
    - Holm, Celeste (Box A-57, Folder 238)
    - Holman, Baxter D. (Box A-57, Folder 239)
      Photographer if identified: Livingstone College/Public Relations Office
    - Holman, Ben (Box A-57, Folder 240)
    - Holman, Carl (See Holman, M. Carl) (Box A-57, Folder 241)
    - Holman, Denise (Box A-57, Folder 242)
    - Holman, Eddie (Box A-57, Folder 243)
    - Holman, Fayleano S. (Mrs.) (Box A-57, Folder 244)
    - Holman, Joe (Box A-57, Folder 245)
    - Holman, M. Carl (Box A-57, Folder 246)
    - Holmes, Adolph (Box A-57, Folder 247)
    - Holmes, Adrienne (Mrs.) (Box A-57, Folder 248)
      Photographer if identified: Edward J. Edahl
    - Holmes, Carl (Box A-57, Folder 249)
    - Holmes, Carolyn (Box A-57, Folder 250)
    - Holmes, Carolyn Dorethea (Box A-57, Folder 251)
    - Holmes, Cecil (Box A-57, Folder 252)
    - Holmes, Clarence (Box A-57, Folder 253)
      Also two velox prints. Also one typescript bio on five leaves.
      Photographer if identified: Board of Education
    - Holmes, Clint (Box A-57, Folder 254)
    - Holmes, Coleman (Box A-57, Folder 255)
    - Holmes, De Field T. (Dr.) (Box A-57, Folder 256)
    - Holmes, Edward H. (Rev.) (Box A-57, Folder 257)
    - Holmes, Ellis B. (Box A-57, Folder 258)
    - Holmes, Ernest (Box A-57, Folder 259)
    - Holmes, Ernie (Box A-57, Folder 260)
    - Holmes, Eugene (Box A-57, Folder 261)
    - Holmes, Florence (Box A-57, Folder 262)
      Photographer if identified: John D. Bunns, News Voice International
    - Holmes, George (Box A-57, Folder 263)
    - Holmes, Groove (Box A-57, Folder 264)
    - Holmes, Hamilton (Box A-57, Folder 265)
    - Holmes, Horace R. (Box A-57, Folder 266)
    - Holmes, Joseph A. (Box A-57, Folder 267)
    - Holmes, Lloyd (Box A-57, Folder 268)
      Photographer if identified: Charles Tilley
    - Holmes, Lorence B. (Dr.) (Box A-57, Folder 269)
    - Holmes, Lucky (Box A-57, Folder 270)
    - Holman, M. Carl (Box A-57, Folder 271)
    - Homer, Ron (Box A-57, Folder 272)
    - Holmes, Margaret (Box A-57, Folder 273)
    - Holmes, Larry (Box A-57, Folder 274)
    - Holmes, Margaret S. (Box A-57, Folder 275)
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert/News Voice International
    - Holmes, Margaret Flagg (Box A-57, Folder 276)
    - Holmes, Margall (Box A-57, Folder 277)